rent-at-avis.com 2009-03-28

# Privacy Statement

****Avis data protection policy**  
**

 **  
** We ask for your name, telephone number and e-mail address. This helps us to process your booking, to contact you if we have any problems with your request or to send you an electronic confirmation of the booking. If you are a Wizard member we link your membership number to the information we keep in our main customer database in order to speed up your booking process. 

We operate the following policy with regard to the privacy of customer data:

We will maintain the personal information provided via this site as part of our records to assist us to maintain and improve our administration and management of our car rental business. As we are part of an international group operating the Avis Rent A Car System, we will from time to time share with other companies operating the Avis Rent A Car System (located inside and outside Europe) information relating to our car rental service operations, which may include the personal information provided via this site. Unless you have given us your consent your personal information will not be used for any other purpose.   
Customers are welcome to see the information held about them at any time and to make the necessary amendments to keep the information up to date. 

To see information please contact marketing@avis.co.uk quoting your name and address. 

******

**What data does Avis collect?**  

**  
**IP address:** We collect your IP address when you visit our site. This only identifies your ISP (Internet Service Provider) and does not contain any information about you as an individual. We use this information to help us understand more about where our site traffic originates. 

******

**How does Avis protect your data?**  

**  
If any security is needed to protect information such as credit card details we use **Secure Socket Layer (SSL** ) technology encryption software. 

******

**On-line promotions**  

**  
If you participate in any competitions or prize draws we offer on our site, we will ask you to enter certain personal information so we can notify you if necessary. Exact terms and conditions or rules of each competition / prize draw will be posted at the time and may vary. If a prize is offered through a third party we may need to disclose information to the relevant third party in order to facilitate the distribution of any prizes.

******

**On-line surveys**  

**  
When you participate in any on-line surveys you may be asked to supply certain personal information, for example demographic data such as age and/or income. You can provide all or none as you so choose. We will use these survey results to improve the site features and usability.  
  
| © 2000-2008 Avis Europe plc.   |   
---|---
